<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="ready">Ready?</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="phone_number">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="sign_up">Sign up</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="clinic_s">Clinic\'s</string>
    <string name="safe_tomatoes">Safe Tomatoes</string>
    <string name="tomato_mosaic_virus">Tomato Mosaic Virus</string>
    <string name="appearance">Appearance</string>
    <string name="tomata_mosaic_ide">The foliage of affected tomato plants shows mottling, with alternating yellowish and darker green areas, the latter often appearing thicker and raised giving a blister-like appearance</string>
    <string name="solution">Solution</string>
    <string name="know_more">Know more</string>
    <string name="target_spot_sol">Remove old plant debris at the end of the growing season; otherwise, the spores will travel from debris to newly planted tomatoes in the following growing season Water tomato plants in the morning so the leaves have time to dry. Water at the base of the plant or use a soaker hose or drip system to keep the leaves dry. Apply a mulch to keep the fruit from coming in direct contact with the soil.</string>
    <string name="target_spot">Target Spot</string>
    <string name="bacterial_spot">Bacterial Spot</string>
    <string name="bacterial_sol">Remove old vegetable debris in the garden and do not plant new crops where host plants were once growing. There are no recognized chemical treatments for bacterial leaf spot disease. Your best bet is prevention and mechanical control at the first sign of symptoms of bacterial leaf spot.</string>
    <string name="bact_val">Bacterial spot appears on leaves as small (less than ⅛ inch), sometimes water-soaked (i.e., wet-looking) circular areas. Spots may initially be yellow-green, but darken to brownish-red as they age.</string>
    <string name="late_blight">Late Blight</string>
    <string name="late_blight_sol">Avoid planting tomatoes on sites that were previously in potatoes or close to potatoes. Sequential planting or planting several crops of tomatoes over time will reduce the risk of late blight destroying all tomatoes at once. Spraying fungicides is the most effective way to prevent late blight.</string>
    <string name="early_blight">Early Blight</string>
    <string name="early_text">Early blight infection starts at the bottom of the plant with leaf spotting and yellowing. Initially, small dark spots form on older foliage near the ground. Leaf spots are round, brown and can grow up to 1/2 inch in diameter.</string>
    <string name="early_sol"><![CDATA[Tomatoes that have early blight require immediate attention before the disease takes over the plants. Thoroughly spray the plant (bottoms of leaves also) with Bonide Liquid Copper Fungicide concentrate or Bonide Tomato & Vegetable. Both of these treatments are organic.]]></string>
    <string name="septoria_leaf_spot">Septoria leaf spot</string>
    <string name="spectoria_sol">Removing infected leaves. Remove infected leaves immediately, and be sure to wash your hands and pruners thoroughly before working with uninfected plants. Consider organic fungicide options what is the best fungicide for Septoria leaf spot? Most fungicides registered for use on tomatoes would effectively control Septoria leaf spot. These include maneb, mancozeb, chlorothalonil, and benomyl.</string>
    <string name="leaf_mold">Leaf Mold</string>
    <string name="leaf_mold_text">Pale greenish-yellow spots, usually less than 1/4 inch, with no definite margins, form on the upper sides of leaves. Olive-green to brown velvety mold forms on the lower leaf surface below leaf spots. Leaf spots grow together and turn brown. Leaves wither and die but often remain attached to the plant.</string>
    <string name="leaf_mold_sol">Applying fungicides when symptoms first appear can reduce the spread of the leaf mold fungus significantly. Several fungicides are labeled for leaf mold control on tomatoes and can provide good disease control if applied to all the foliage of the plant, especially the lower surfaces of the leaves.</string>
    <string name="solution1">SOLUTION</string>
    <string name="for_treatment_advice">For Treatment Advice</string>
    <string name="click_here">Click here</string>
    <string name="select_the_city">Select the city</string>
    <string name="to_visit">To visit</string>
    <string name="tamil_nadu_agricultural_university">Tamil Nadu Agricultural University</string>
    <string name="annamalai_university">Annamalai University</string>
    <string name="college_of_agricultural_technology_theni">College Of Agricultural Technology, Theni</string>
    <string name="agricultural_college_and_research_institute_kudumiyanmalai">Agricultural College and Research Institute, Kudumiyanmalai</string>
    <string name="adhiparasakthi_agricultural_college_apac">Adhiparasakthi Agricultural College (APAC)</string>
    <string name="vanavarayar_institute_of_agriculture_via">Vanavarayar Institute of Agriculture (VIA)</string>
    <string name="rvs_agricultural_college">RVS Agricultural College</string>
    <string name="don_bosco_college_of_agriculture">Don Bosco College of Agriculture</string>
    <string name="sethu_bhaskara_agricultural_college_and_research_foundation">Sethu Bhaskara Agricultural College and Research Foundation</string>
    <string name="not_listed_click_here">Not Listed Click here</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
</resources>